SIRISHA DEVATHA () Featured

Software Consultant seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Cloud Computing, Project Management, Web Development, System Analysis, Business Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Shell Scripting, Basic Java and worked in Oracle Tech apps.



Current Designation: Software Consultant Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Hitachi Vantara Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: MS Software Engineering [IT]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad, Other

International Location

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Consultant, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Cloud Computing, Project Management, Web Development, System Analysis, Business Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Shell

Scripting, SQL, Java, Oracle, PLSQL

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Over 5 years of experience as an Oracle Apps Techno Functional Consultant.

Worked on Oracle Cloud Implementation, Oracle R12 Implementation and Support Projects.

Worked on Order Management, Inventory and Service Modules.

Proficient in designing and developing custom solutions and extensions to Oracle ERP and Oracle Cloud.

Work Experience

Hitachi Consulting as Software Engineer Jul 2014 to Jun 2019

Software Consultant

Hitachi Vantara as Software Consultant Jul 2014 to Jun 2019

Worked in Oracle EBS,Oracle Support, Implementation,Oracle cloud,BI Publisher reports,XML reports with 5yrs of experience

Hitachi Vantara as Software Consultant Jul 2014 to Till Date

Education

PG: MS Software Engineering (IT) from Vellore Institute of Technology (VIT) in 2014

1/22/2021

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Sales force Administrator

A+ N+ CCNA certified

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
oracle 10g/11i/R12	
SQL, PL/SQL, Basic Java	
Oracle Applications R12	
ORACLE FUSION APPLICATIONS	
Report Builder, PL/SQL Queries	
Unix Shell Scripting, SQL Loader	
Conversions, XML Publisher	
Discoverer 10g and Discoverer 11i	
Cloud Taleo.	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
Hindi				
Telugu	Expert			
English				
Tamil				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time